Jin,
I really like you.
You know how hot Jin is, right?
You've been practicing hard all day,
so I bought you some water.
Are you...
really serious about my friend?
Does it look like I'm not?
I told you to pretend to flirt with me.
Don't get too into it.
I mean, I don't like pretending.
If you have something to say, just say it.
I'm going to hit on you for real.
No pretending this time.
I'd like to dedicate this award to all of you.
How honorable is
that trophy of yours anyway?
Do you even realize
that you're the real problem in this family?
I do.
To you, someone only counts as family
if they're useful to you, and that's it.
Honey...
Do you think my dad
will ever be able to accept me?
I just feel like
I'll never get to be myself
as long as I'm still in this world.
It's because you never cared about him.
If there's anything else I can do
to help with Anda,
let me know.
I'm really not crying.
I know. Why don't you go wash up
in my room first?
What are you looking at?
Someone who isn't crying.
You're quite the teaser, aren't you?
My friend just died.
Just let me cry.
I think of him every time I'm driving.
Jin.
You might not know this,
but I really like Anda as an actor.
He was my source of happiness.
I felt sad when people criticized him.
I felt happy when they praised him.
When this happened to him,
I could barely stand it.
If you're sad, you can just show it.
You don't have to worry
about how anyone sees you.
He was your best friend after all.
Everyone understands you.
Can I give you a hug?
♫When we happened to hold hands,
was that when it all started?♫
♫When I somehow memorized your number,
was that when you took my heart?♫
♫Never knew you'd have my heart from the start♫
♫But today...♫
What are you guys doing?
I'm just stretching.
[The depicted characters, behaviors, locations,
organizations, professions, and events]
[are fictional and created
for entertainment purposes only.]
[It is not intended to endorse or promote
any of the actions or behavior depicted.]
[Viewer discretion is advised.]
♫I used to wonder what we were,♫
♫I thought love needed something clearer,♫
♫Took me time to learn what really matters♫
♫Love has no rules, whatever comes after♫
♫As long as I know what my heart wants to find,♫
♫As long as you're standing by my side,♫
♫With you, the only one I'd choose every time,♫
♫I don't need a reason, as long as you're mine♫
♫As long as you hold my hand,♫
♫As long as next to me is where you stand,♫
♫You're the one I'll always try to understand,♫
♫No matter how hard the road may be,♫
♫Just hold my hand, and we'll be free♫
♫As long as you're here with me♫
Point B.
1.462...
62...
0.132...
So, what actually happened, Jin?
Was it really a murder?
I don't know.
I only know as much as you guys do.
People on the internet
are just guessing away.
But I think there's some truth to the idea
that Anda might not have taken his life.
Yeah.
I don't think he did it, either.
That's Anda we're talking about.
Our friend, Anda.
Jin,
what do you think?
He definitely didn't take his life.
That's all I know.
Hey!
Got bored of your phone or something?
You just tossed it away.
Well, you just showed up out of nowhere.
- You startled me.
- I was calling you from way over there.
You were sitting here spacing out.
You're allowed to grieve over Anda's death,
but don't waste your feelings
on those crazy people online.
I don't want to overthink it,
but have you seen what they're saying?
They're saying
Anda was just trying to get attention.
See?
That's what I meant. Give it to me.
I know you're sad,
but there's nothing we can do.
Do you understand, Podduang?
Why?
He was in so much pain.
Why did his life have to end like this?
Even after he's gone,
people still won't stop hurting him.
I understand,
but there's nothing we can do.
Let me see.
Are you crying?
I'm not.
Look at you.
We're the same age,
but why do I feel like you're still a kid?
Maybe it's because you're big.
Is that an insult?
I'm your best friend, you know.
Return this for me.
Thanks a lot, Dunk.
Here, have something sweet.
Anyway, this helps.
Every time she sends me a screenshot,
the battery is in the red.
But wait...
There are kiosks everywhere.
I borrowed it for you,
and now I have to return it?
Why? Can't you just do that for me?
Fine, I will.
What are you smiling at?
Yeah, you've been smiling for a while now.
It's just that...
I'm glad to have you two as my friends.
Oh, is something the matter?
I didn't see you at lunch,
so I came up to check on you.
And you're not eating?
If you were in my shoes,
would you be able to eat anything?
My brother just died.
If you're not feeling up to it,
you can take a break.
I'll take care of this case myself.
Don't worry.
And...
did you find anything else?
I'm going through the CCTV footage.
He parked in a very secluded spot,
so I have to check it thoroughly.
Anyway,
the forensic report says
he died of suffocation.
Did your brother
often fall asleep in the car?
Yes.
When he was sleepy,
he tended to just pass out.
Actually, my mom had warned him about it.
I'm being serious here.
You also think
this doesn't look like suicide, right?
Yeah, I've been thinking the same thing.
I know that depression is unpredictable,
but I don't think that's the case here
even though he had to
take sleeping pills regularly.
That's right.
They found that it was
a very mild type of sleeping pill,
and there wasn't a large amount
in his system.
I was actually the last person to see him.
Why did I let him drive all by himself?
Where did you part ways with your brother?
At a restaurant near our house.
As I said,
Anda moved out to live in a condo,
so I had to make plans
to meet up with him and catch up.
He seemed perfectly fine, though.
We were both acting very normal.
I was even complaining to him
about how he used my car
but wouldn't go get it washed.
Why?
What happened, Lieutenant?
Itti,
I promise you
that if someone is behind this incident,
I'll make sure they end up behind bars.
You don't have to worry at all.
My team and I
are willing to do our best for you.
Thank you very much, Lieutenant.
If you find out where he went
after parting ways with me
or who he met,
please report it to me.
I might be able to provide some information.
My family and I
will cooperate fully.
Of course.
Stop reading the comments on Anda's news.
These netizens are just talking nonsense.
It's not like there are many.
Most of them are just asking
about the cause of death.
What do you think, though?
Do you think Anda was murdered?
On today's topic,
- regarding actor Anda's death,
- I think...
- it's possible that he was murdered.
- police are currently investigating
to determine the cause of death
and establish what happened.
Preliminary forensic findings indicate that
the cause of death
may have been suffocation.
However, authorities are continuing
to examine the evidence
and gather further details
to conclude the cause of death.
Oh...
Amp, are you taking out the trash?
Yes.
Are you okay, Amp?
Anda didn't take his life.
Anda didn't kill himself.
It's true!
We need to help him.
Find the culprit.
We need to help Anda. We must help him.
She was talking like she was out of it.
Then she suddenly ran into her room.
I didn't even get to ask her anything.
I'm so confused.
She's a fan,
so she must be grieving, too.
That's why she's been acting a bit off.
I'm a fan, too.
I've been moping all day.
Podduang,
do you also think
that Anda was murdered?
Yeah, I think so, too.
How about we find out the truth together?
What truth?
The truth about...
who actually killed him.
Please, Podduang.
Help me find them.
Consider it a final favor for Anda.
Yeah, let's help Anda.
Podduang,
have you eaten anything?
I have.
And have you slept at all?
It's the one I borrowed.
And you just bought a new one?
Yeah.
I lost yours,
so I bought a new one to replace it.
You guys don't have to worry about me.
I can eat and sleep,
but...
I just can't stop thinking about it.
How can I help you?
Bumm...
What the hell is this?
What is it?
[Breaking! Leaked Messages of Deceased Star
May Hold Clues to His Death]
[Let's break up, Anda.]
[What happened, Kum? What's wrong?]
[I'm sorry, Anda.]
[Kum, you're not like this. What's wrong?]
[Let's break up, Anda.]
[Does anyone know Anda's boyfriend? Who is he?]
[Is the chat real or edited?]
[Is Kum involved in Anda's death?]
[Stop guessing blindly, please.]
[What do you mean blindly? They broke up
on the day he died. Is that a coincidence?]
[Was this the reason he took his own life?]
[Please respect the deceased and the family.]
Is that chat real?
Is this person named Kum
involved in this matter?
I only know as much as you do.
And what do you think?
I don't think it was Kum.
Why are you so sure?
I know him. He wouldn't do it.
How can you trust someone so easily?
[Interrogation Room]
When was the last time you saw the deceased?
In the morning...
before he left the condo.
Were you two living together?
Yes.
We were dating.
Where were you throughout that day?
Did you meet the deceased again?
Where were you?
I...
I had something to do at a friend's house.
Do you know
where the deceased's phone and laptop are?
I don't.
I...
searched all over the condo
but couldn't find them...
as I already said.
Do you know
the phone passcode of the deceased?
I do.
He knew mine, too.
Do you know
where the deceased's phone and laptop are?
I don't know, officer.
I told you already.
Then can you tell me
who the friend you visited that day was?
I can't tell you.
If you provide us
with information that could help,
it'll be better for both you
and your boyfriend's case.
You're aware of that, right?
So why can't you tell us where you were?
Personal reasons.
Then can you guess
if anyone else
might be involved in Anda's death?
I really don't know, officer.
Are we really going to meet Kum, Jin?
Yeah.
They're still interrogating him right now,
and I don't know when they'll be finished.
I don't know.
It's better than doing nothing.
You haven't changed your mind, have you?
Do you still think Kum's not the culprit?
Yeah, I still think so.
Oh...
- Hello.
What are you guys doing here?
We've come to see Kum.
Has he left yet?
He's still being interrogated.
Why are you guys looking for Kum?
Itti,
we're certain that Kum isn't the culprit.
Let the police handle it.
You shouldn't vouch for anyone.
But Itti,
we're actually very close to Kum.
Those two really loved each other.
It's impossible.
They were in love.
There's no way
he would hurt Anda like that.
But he's not cooperating at all.
He's being very suspicious
and won't answer any questions.
We haven't been able to let him leave yet.
I think he probably has his reasons,
but he definitely wouldn't hurt Anda.
Did Kum and Anda...
ever have any problems?
Hey.
I'll never break up with you, Anda.
No matter what, I won't.
They never fought at all.
They really loved each other.
Anyway, let the police handle this matter.
You guys can go home now.
I'll be going, then.
- Goodbye.
What now?
I don't know.
Art, what on earth are you doing?
Oh...
I've seen you fumbling with that
for a while.
Oh, I was recording.
I saw it in a movie.
They said that no matter what happens,
you should always record it.
Record for what?
Well,
it's for evidence.
Just in case we miss something,
we can listen to it again.
Does anyone have earphones?
Let me borrow them.
I think I do. Just a sec.
Thanks.
One each.
Turn up the volume.
I can't hear a thing, Art.
Yeah.
Are your earbuds broken, Podduang?
What?
How could that be possible?
Dunk just bought me these.
Could it be a knock-off?
In the livestreams I watch,
they always sell items that failed QC.
Better be careful.
You complain so much.
You're using someone else's thing,
and you're complaining?
Here, Podduang. Take it.
I have an idea.
I'll put it on the computer in my room
so I can listen to it like a detective.
You're way too into these series.
- Let's go.
- Hey.
Let's go.
See ya. We're heading out.
- See ya.
- See you later.
Let's get going.
I'll give you a ride.
Keep watching the series.
We're reaching the climax.
Oh, are we?
- No, that climax.
- We're reaching the climax, right?
- Kum...
- Look, it's almost at the climax.
Kum...
I want us to go public.
It's up to you, Anda.
As for me, I can handle it anyway.
See?
You're always like this.
How could I not love
this old golden retriever of mine?
Anda...
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Lieutenant, what do you think
about that Kum guy?
No matter how you look at it, it's strange.
If we just had a bit more time,
we could have gotten something from him.
If it wasn't for the law,
I wouldn't have let him go.
By the way, aren't you close to him at all?
I heard he's been dating your brother
for a long time.
Not at all.
Anda never brought him to meet me.
They moved out to live together.
But if Kum is involved in Anda's death,
I won't let him get away with it.
You know that, right?
I'm so hungry.
There's nothing to eat in my room.
Do you want anything?
No, you go ahead.
You're really not eating?
Yeah.
Then...
I'm getting some.
What are you looking at?
[Jinna: Can I have your beer?]
I sent you a message.
You didn't reply.
I know.
Just a moment.
Why are you giving me this?
What?
Look.
You said you wanted a beer.
[Jinna: Can I have your beer?]
Yeah, a beer it is.
But I can't ride home if I drink this.
I know.
I'll drink with you.
Get on the bike.
What are you standing there for?
Can you hold this?
How would I ride the bike?
I need both hands on the handlebar.
Come here, let me put it on for you.
Gotta wear a helmet to stay safe on the road.
Get on.
Here, you go first,
or you won't be able to get on.
Is Satang coming back late again?
Yeah.
He's staying at a friend's house tonight.
I guess they'll be gaming all night again.
He never stays home, does he?
If you see him,
give him a piece of your mind for me.
He really looks up to you.
So, did drinking beer help with the stress?
Why do I have to drink beer
only when I'm stressed?
Why would you think that?
Well, you texted me asking for a beer,
so I thought you were stressed.
Oh...
It was autocorrect.
Look.
[Can I have your numbeer?]
[Can I have your beer?]
Oh...
I was wondering
why you suddenly asked for a beer.
I was going to ask for your number.
Number?
Like, my number?
Yeah.
What for?
Well, I want it.
How many reasons are there
for someone to ask for a number?
Plenty.
You could be trying to sell me insurance.
Or...
you might be a scammer.
I bet that's it.
That's your side job, huh?
You're weird.
What if it's because I wanna make a move?
Make a move?
On me?
I asked for your number
to hit on your brother, I guess.
Smartass.
I won't give it to you, then.
Does "it" mean your number
or permission to hit on you?
Both.
Can I kiss you, Podduang?
♫When we happened to hold hands,
was that when it all started?♫
♫When I somehow memorized your number,
was that when you took my heart?♫
♫Never knew you'd have my heart from the start♫
♫But today, hiding these feelings
suddenly feels so hard♫
♫I'm caught off guard, I don't know what to do,♫
♫So let me just tell you how much I love you♫
♫I fell for you right out of the blue,♫
♫Out of nowhere, I fell for you♫
♫I have no clue when I started feeling this way♫
♫Yet somehow, I fell for you anyway♫
♫All I know is I'm loving you more every day♫
♫Could it be my heart chose you
from the first day?♫
I...
I'd better leave.
♫Is missing you what love feels like?♫
♫You're always on my mind,♫
♫Whatever I do,
I think of you all day and night,♫
♫I guess this is what love feels like♫
Forgot my phone.
♫I thought I was just lonely, nothing more,♫
♫Then you came so casually,
like you'd done it before,♫
♫You're simply being yourself,
yet somehow I fall,♫
♫So, wanna give it a try and be my all?♫
♫I'm caught off guard, I don't know what to do,♫
♫So let me just tell you how much I love you♫
♫I fell for you right out of the blue,♫
♫Out of nowhere, I fell for you♫
♫I have no clue when I started feeling this way♫
♫Yet somehow, I fell for you anyway♫
♫All I know is I'm loving you more every day♫
♫Could it be my heart chose you
from the first day?♫
Are they really broken?
Dunk, you asshole.
I won't let you borrow my things ever again.
Help me.
Help...
Are you sure it wasn't music?
Yeah.
It's just like I told you.
It came from the earbuds.
Help me,
Jin...
Hey, Jin.
Do you believe me?
I'm not crazy.
The sound really came from the earbuds.
It was so clear.
It's like...
someone was speaking right in my ear.
Then, would you believe me...
if I told you that...
I've heard those voices
for as long as I can remember?
Jin...
Your time is up.
Don't cross the road.
Jin...
Your time is up.
Help me,
Jin.
Your time is up.
Jin, help me.
Those voices won't stop ringing in my head.
There's nothing I can do about them.
That's why I know
that you're not just imagining it...
because I've been hearing those voices, too.
Those voices?
The voice you heard from the earbuds...
is Anda's.
It's the same voice
I've been hearing for a while now.
That's not funny, Jin.
This isn't something to joke about.
Where do you think it came from, then?
I'm not joking, Podduang.
Just believe me.
Anda is still lingering around us.
He really needs our help.
Anda,
if there's anything I can do to help,
let me know.
Who did this to you?
Let me help you, Anda.
Your brother just died, Itti.
Won't you even give me time to process this?
Mom,
I understand,
but look at what this is doing to you.
You can't eat or sleep at all.
You're going to keep drowning in grief forever.
I'm worried about you and Dad.
Anda is already gone.
But as for us,
we still have to live on.
Then give me one month
before we cremate him.
Mom,
please let him go.
Itti...
Why won't you listen to me at all?
I asked for three months, and you said no.
Now I'm asking for just one month,
and you still say no.
You're really...
a terrible brother.
You couldn't even protect your brother.
I'm asking for more time with him,
and you won't let me have it.
Fine, then it's up to you.
Hey, want to go to that same place after this?
We need to talk about Anda again.
Hello, Satang?
I'm at the funeral.
Sure.
Say that again.
What happened to the kitchen sink?
The water won't stop running.
I even turned the red valve
like you told me to.
What?
Are you sure you turned it the right way?
How could it still be running?
I turned it the right way!
I turned it so hard it almost broke.
Wait, hold on.
Just a second.
Hey.
Can you hear me?
Hello, Satang?
What the hell?
Hello?
Hey, hello?
Satang, hello?
Podduang...
Help me.
Was it you?
You killed him, didn't you?
You planned the whole thing, didn't you?
Say something!
Why aren't you saying anything?
Just answer me!
Don't be a coward!
I didn't do it.
You didn't?
Then what the hell was that chat?
What did you tell the police?
Spit it out!
I told you already.
I've told them everything.
You've told them everything?
- Enough already.
- Enough.
Go.
Shit...
This is my brother's funeral.
If you're going to fight like rabid dogs,
take it outside.
- Aren't you a cop?
- Go.
You should put him in jail!
He's the one who killed Anda.
Just confess already.
- Tell everyone you killed him!
- Stop it.
That's enough.
This is going too far.
My parents are sitting right there.
At the very least, show them some respect.
Do you really think...
that Anda killed himself?
What I think is none of your business.
As for a partner like you,
who only cares about losing your job
because my brother is dead,
go throw your tantrum somewhere else.
Don't do it at my brother's funeral.
Do you get it now?
If you do, please leave.
You ruined my life.
You bastard!
Go.
Leave.
Podduang!
I don't care
whether or not you like Jin.
He doesn't belong to anyone yet,
so let's compete to win him over.
Deal?
Do you want anything?
I'll get it for you.
I can buy it myself.
But I'm sure there's something
that you really want
but money can't buy.
The jacket the vendor is wearing...
I bought it for Anda.
How did my friend's jacket end up with you?
I took it from...
From the dead man's car, right?
♫I used to wonder what we were,♫
♫I thought love needed something clearer,♫
♫Took me time to learn what really matters♫
♫Love has no rules, whatever comes after♫
♫As long as I know what my heart wants to find,♫
♫As long as you're standing by my side,♫
♫With you, the only one I'd choose every time,♫
♫I don't need a reason, as long as you're mine♫
♫As long as you hold my hand,♫
♫As long as next to me is where you stand,♫
♫You're the one I'll always try to understand,♫
♫No matter how hard the road may be,♫
♫Just hold my hand, and we'll be free♫
♫As long as you're here with me♫
♫I rest my hands, holding on to yours♫
♫You chased away my uncertainty♫
♫No words were said, but I hear you♫
♫Loud and clear, it's meant to be♫
♫As long as I know what my heart wants to find,♫
♫As long as you're standing by my side,♫
♫With you, the only one I'd choose every time,♫
♫I don't need a reason, as long as you're mine♫
♫As long as you hold my hand,♫
♫As long as next to me is where you stand,♫
♫You're the one I'll always try to understand,♫
♫No matter how hard the road may be,♫
♫Just hold my hand, and we'll be free♫
♫As long as you're here with me♫
♫As long as next to me is where you stand,♫
♫You're the one I'll always try to understand,♫
♫No matter how hard the road may be,♫
♫Just hold my hand, and we'll be free♫
♫As long as you're here with me♫